<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">IndijiSites</string>
    
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    
    <string name="menu_legalnotices">Legal Notices</string>
    
    <string name="map_not_ready">Map is not ready yet.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_bris">This is Brisbane</string>
    
    <string name="name_brisbane">Brisbane</string>
    
    <string name="transparency">transparency</string>
    
    <string name="murray_river_desc">For thousands of years many Aboriginal
         people have relied on the Murray River for resources. Many scarred
          trees (canoes crafted from River Red gums), banks of river rich
           with sites including rock art, shields and other artefacts.</string>
           
    <string name="Purnululu_desc">55 km south of Turkey Creek rock paintings 
        are found in some of the shelters, caves and gorges.. Motifs being 
        ancestral beings from the Dreamtime, crocodiles, fish and stencils 
        of children\'s hands. Few are available for public viewing.</string>
        
    <string name="sandy_national_desc">Aboriginal people have been fishing 
        and collecting shellfish on Fraser Island for more than a thousand 
        years and many of their middens can be seen along the east coast."</string>
        
    <string name="red_hands_desc">This Red Hands Cave site is one of the best 
        examples of Aboriginal art in the Blue Mountains National Park.
        The cave is a gallery of fine hand stencils and hand prints, 
        created between 500 and 1600 years ago. Many of the stencils 
        and prints overlap, making it difficult to see how many hands 
        there are. Stencils are also a sign of respect for Country, 
        and have a deep spiritual connection with the land. To make 
        the stencils, Aboriginal people placed one hand against the 
        cave wall and blew a mixture of ochre and water from their mouths. 
        When the hand was removed, a stencilled outline was left behind. 
        At other times, people covered their hands with ochre and placed them on the wall, 
        leaving an imprint.</string>
        
    <string name ="birrigai_desc">Is the oldest known Aboriginal site in the ACT (Ngunnawal people).</string>
        
    <string name="chillagoe_desc">Open to the public are rockshelters with rock art such as Balancing Rock.</string>
    
    <string name="mtcameron_desc">One of the most important Aboriginal art sites in Tasmania.
         Geometric motiffs cover nearly every inch of rock. Numerous deeply sculpted circles
          and other motiffs.</string>
    
    <string name="innamincka_desc">Large Aboriginal Stone Quarry sites around Innamincka.</string>
    
    <string name="nullplain_desc">About 40 Aboriginal Sites, hand stencils, stone artefacts
         and stone arrangements.</string>
    
    <string name="uluru_desc">Uluru, the most distinctive symbol of the Australian landscape. 
        The park consists of two outstanding features- Uluru and the dramatic rock domes of Kata 
        Tjuta( the Mount Olga group). Aboriginal owners of the rock are the Pitjantjatjara and 
        Yankunytjatjara people. The caves around the base of Uluru are adorned with hundreds of 
        rock paintings.</string>
    
</resources>